Katelyn Lange

3219 Lockport Rd, Sanborn NY 14132 716-807-9094 | Ikatelyn6109@gmail.com

Daniel Greer
Area Director for Greek Circle, Racquet Club, and University Commons
Center for Residence Life
Rochester Institute of Technology

Dear Mr. Greer:

Please accept this letter as an application regarding for the position of an assistantship for the 2013-2014 academic year. I am interested in becoming more involved in the RIT community.

I am currently pursuing a Bachelor of Science Degree in Architectural Technology at Alfred State SUNY College of Technology and as stated in my resume have experience with an internship and many jobs that will help me in doing an assistantship. Through my education, I have experience working with many computer programs, such as the Microsoft Office Suite. Through my working experience, I am very accommodating and can conduct myself in a professional manner. As indicated in my resume, I have accomplished many things such as a member of the Alfred State Honors Program, Alfred State Deans List, and maintaining the Excellence in Education Scholarship.

A brief resume is enclosed that will demonstrate my ambition and strong desire for the advancement in my education. I look forward to learn more about the position and will contact you next week to ensure the receipt of my resume and hopefully arrange an interview.

Best Regards,

Katelyn Lange

	Katelyn Lange
	3219 Lockport Rd, Sanborn NY 14132
	716-807-9094 Ikatelyn6109@gmail.com
Education	l
09 2009 - 05 2013	Alfred State SUNY College of Technology
	Architectural Technology
	Bachelor of Science
Awards	
09 2009 - 05 2013	Alfred State College Honors Program
	Alfred State College Dean's List
	Excellence in Education Scholarship
Work Experience	
05 2012 - 08 2012 05 2010 - Present	Wendel Companies Buffalo, NY Architectural Intern
	Assisted architects and project managers with construction documents in preparation
	for client presentations and organized and researched material library. Dunkin' Donuts Sanborn, NY Crew Member
	Provided excellent customer service and trained new employees of company
	procedures. Responsible for closing and opening shifts and handling cash drawers.
05 2008 - 08 2009	Town of Wheatfield Recreation Wheatfield, NY Recreational Aide
	Planned and prepared activities for children in the Town of Wheatfield Youth Center.
	Coordinated and volunteered for events for the Town of Wheatfield.
Extra-Curricular	
08 2010 - Present	WINS Treasurer
	WINS (Women In Non-traditional Studies) is a student organization that focuses on
	women in the work field. The organization includes community service and events for
	Alfred State College.
01 2012 - Present	Alfred State College Administration Student Caller
	Reach out to prospective students on events at Alfred State College and inform them
	on the application process.
09 2012 - 05 2012	Alfred State College Administration Student Host
	Hosted high school students overnight that were interested in attending Alfred State
	College. Educated prospective students on campus life and participated in a variety of
C	activities, including campus tours.
Community Service	
	St. Peter's Lutheran Church Sanborn, NY Vacation Bible School
	Developed and taught lessons to children from all Lutheran churches in the area.
	St. Peter's Lutheran Church Sanborn, NY College Student Bible Study
	Attend bible studies and conduct community service opportunities for local charities,
Tachnical Chille	including the Niagara Gospel Rescue Mission.
Technical Skills	Povit AutoCAD Google Sketch up Adobe Photochen Microsoft Office
	Revit, AutoCAD, Google Sketch up, Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft Office,
	Modeling, Hand Drafting, Presentation Layouts